niki.ai 2019-05-29

# Niki - India's Own Chatbot For Online Transactions | Making It As Simple As Talking To A Friend

We at Niki, a brand of Techbins Solutions Private Limited (referred to as ‘we’, ‘us’, ‘our’, ‘Niki’, ‘Techbins’) is concerned about the privacy of its users (hereinafter referred to as ‘Buyers’, ‘Users’, ‘You’, ‘Your’, ‘Yourself’) accessing its App and has provided this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to familiarise You with the manner in which Niki collects, acquires, uses and discloses Your information collected through the App.

By using the App, you agree to the Terms & Conditions and the Privacy Policy. In case you have any doubts, clarifications you may contact us at [info@niki.ai](mailto:info@niki.ai). If you do not agree to the Agreement and policy, please do not make use of the App.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

This Policy explains how Niki collects personal and non-personal information, classified as mandatory or voluntary and uses, discloses and protects such information through the App. Personal Information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy shall include, but not limited to, information regarding Your name, address, mobile number, date of birth, gender, age, e-mail address, photo or other information. It is mandatory to register using some or all Personal Information and you may choose to not use the App in case of reservation to provide the information. It is solely your decision to register or not register for the services and by agreeing to the Policy, you understand the risk associated and agree to abide by it.

You may provide more Personal Information to Niki during the course of usage of the App such as but not limited to alternative phone numbers, addresses, payment details, messages, reviews, feedbacks or any other information. When you use Niki’s Service through its App, Niki may use Your mobile device’s ID (the unique identification assigned to a mobile device by the manufacturer). Niki does this to store your preferences and track your use of Niki App. You understand and agree that Niki has every right to share such details, ID with third parties for its promotions, analysis, etc. Niki collects Your Personal Information in order to record, support and facilitate Your participation in the activities You select, track Your preferences, to provide You with a customized App experience, to notify You of any updated information and new activities and other related functions offered by Niki that might interest you, keep You informed about latest content available on the App, special offers, and other products and services of Niki, to assist You with customer service or technical support issues, to follow up with You after Your visit, to otherwise support Your relationship with Niki or to prevent fraud and unlawful use.

When you participate in any activities or chats with Niki, you may provide information that might be Personal and it is stored with Niki.

You expressly acknowledge, agree and understand that in order to provide Services, Niki, may from time to time, access Your contact list and/or SMS data on your mobile device to collect, use your contact list or SMS data in accordance with the Privacy Policy. Niki collects your SMS and contact data with the sole purpose of providing a personalized experience on the app. For instance, Niki might provide user the ability to perform recharge for a contact just by entering his name, add a contact to an ongoing conversation with Niki or provide a reminder regarding your impending postpaid bill due date by reading your operators message. Niki collects users SMS and contacts data via a secure interface (HTTPS), the data is used to help user make quicker transactions and to provide personalized reminders and recommendations, the data is used internally only and is not shared with any external parties. The data is being processed in an automated manner and is not exposed or visible to any human, either internal or external to Niki.

By permitting us to collect information regarding Your contacts and SMS data, you hereby agree to provide Niki a right to use such information for providing Services and also warrant that you have all requisite rights in your favour to share this information with Niki.

When You use the App, Niki’s servers may be hosted by a third party service provider may collect information indirectly and automatically about Your activities on the App; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's device hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information You submit to Niki.

Whether You want Your device to accept cookies or not is up to You. If You haven't changed Your device's settings, most likely Your browser already accepts cookies. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience all features of the App. You can also delete Your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact Your experience with the App and may make parts of the App non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that You leave them turned on. The decision to leave them on or off is solely lies with you.

There may be brands listed on the App who might collect information about the Your visits. We may be required to pass on your Personal Information to the brands to fulfil the products and services offered to you. This may include Personal Information or Order specific information or both.

Niki may provide your Personal Information to the brands for fulfilment of any search, discovery, order and any other products and services availed by you.

## SECURITY AND PROTECTION

Niki makes use of third party servers to store information. The servers may be prone to virus, hacks, attacks and your Personal Information may be at risk. Niki strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. For this purpose, Niki adopts appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Niki stores Your personal data. Niki is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive Your Personal Information. The App also linked to many other sites and we shall not be responsible for their privacy policies or practices as it is beyond our control. Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, Niki shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event.

## DISCLOSURE

Niki may disclose any information that it may have about You (including Your identity) if Niki determines that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding Your use of the App or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Niki's rights or property, or the rights or property of users of the App, including Niki’s customers.

## ACCEPTANCE TO POLICY

By using the App, you accept this policy and you agree to provide Personal Information and non-personal information and allow Niki to use it for marketing, strategy, targeting, analytics, audits, fulfilment, communication or any other such activity required by Niki at its sole discretion.

## CHANGES TO POLICY

Niki has and will continue to have the right to modify, change or update Privacy Policy at any time. However, Niki will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with Policy at the time you shared Personal Information. You are encouraged to check the policy often to get updated about privacy policy.

## GRIEVANCE

If you have any questions about the Policy, you may write to us at [info@niki.ai](mailto:info@niki.ai) to get clarification and we shall try to revert back at the earliest to solve your queries.
